A Finding Aid to the Audrey Flack Papers, 1950-2009, in the Archives of American Art AAA.flacaudr
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1966-circa 2007; Series 5; 5.2 Linear feet Boxes 6-11
  - Queen Catherine Sculpture, Queens, New York
    - Queen Catherine Sculpture, 1995-2007; undated; 5 Videocassettes (VHS); 2 Videocassettes (Hi8); 3 Sound cassettes; 1 Electronic discs (DVD) (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Rock Hill Gateway, South Carolina, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Safety Center, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Saint-Gaudens Lecture, Allentown Art Museum, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Saints and Other Angels: The Religious Paintings of Audrey Flack, Lowery Sims, 1986-1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Sarasota County Art in Public Places, Selby Library Project Jury Meeting (2000 November 16), 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - South Pasadena Stroll, Grand Opening Ceremonies of Galatea Garden (2000 November 3), 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Studio Art Centers International, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Film Projects, undated; 2 Film reels 8 mm (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Georgia, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - University of South Florida, "Audrey Flack: Works on Paper", 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Veritas Sculpture, Tampa, Florida, 2000-2007 (Box 11, Folder 7-10)
  - Women's Organizations, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - World War II, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Project Files, circa 2007; undated; 2 Videocassettes (VHS); 1 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Printed Material, 1950-2008; Series 6; 4.1 Linear feet Boxes 11-16, OV 17
  Printed material includes exhibition catalogs for solo and group shows in the United States and abroad, invitations and announcements, press releases, and scattered monographs. Reproductions include postcards featuring Flack's paintings. Exhibition posters include Flack's solo exhibition at the Roko Gallery in 1963. News and magazine clippings document Flack's professional activities over a forty year period. Periodicals contain reviews of Flack's work and announcements of gallery and museum openings. Found is a 1981 review "On Carlo Crivelli" written by Audrey Flack. Miscellaneous printed material consists of scattered announcements, invitations, commencement program, brochures, a press packet, and clippings.
  Materials are arranged by format. Items within each folder are arranged in rough chronological order.
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1952-1977; undated (Box 11, Folder 14-19)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1979-2007 (Box 12, Folder 1-16)
  - Other Catalogs, 1991-1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Invitations and Announcements, circa 1950-2005 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
  - Press Releases, circa 1966-1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Reproductions, circa 1978-1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Oversized material housed in Box 16
  - Posters, circa 1963-2008 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Oversized material housed in Box 16, OV 17
  - News Clippings, circa 1964-2008 (Box 13, Folder 8-22)
  - Magazine Clippings, circa 1980-2005 (Box 13, Folder 23-26)
  - Periodicals, 1965-1976 (Box 13, Folder 27-30)
  - Periodicals, 1977-2007 (Box 14, Folder 1-12)
  - Books, 1991-1996; undated (Box 14, Folder 13-15)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1973-2004; undated (Box 14, Folder 16-21)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Reproductions from Box 13, Folder 6, 1978-1993 (Box 16)
  - Oversized Posters from Box 13, Folder 7, circa 1981-2008 (Box 16)
  - Oversized Periodical from Box 13, Folder 27, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Oversized Periodicals from Box 14, Folders 3, 10, 1999; 1983 (Box 16)
  - Oversized Posters from Box 13, Folder 7, circa 1963-1982 (Box OV 17)
- Scrapbooks, 1977-2008; Series 7; 2 Folders Box 15
  This series contains two scrapbooks. Scrapbook 1 includes scattered materials: a few letters, one from Flack to the New York Times, an excerpt of a review, clippings used for art reference, a press release, an exhibition invitation, membership cards, and digital prints of the artist's sculptures. There is a 1969 press release for "Paintings from the Photo," at the Riverside Museum, one of the first shows devoted to Photorealism. Scrapbook 2 provides partial documentation on the making of the Queen Catherine sculpture and contains sketches and on-site installation photographs.
  - Scrapbook 1, 1977-2008 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook 2, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Photographs, 1966-2009; Series 8; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 15-16
  Photographs include black and white portraits of Mexican laborers taken by Audrey Flack in the mid-1960s, presumably used as source imagery. Also found are photographs of Audrey Flack, by herself, in her studio, and with colleagues and students. There is a photograph of Flack painting the portrait of Anwar Sadat and an inscribed photograph of Flack meeting President Jimmy Carter. Photographs of artwork include images of details from Flack's Photorealist paintings. Polaroid photos document the stages of the glazing and finishing processes in the casting of Civitas.
  Photographs are arranged by subject.
  - By Audrey Flack, circa 1966-circa 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Of Audrey Flack, circa 1969-2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Audrey Flack's Studio, circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Artwork, circa 1970-circa 1995 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Oversized material in Box 16
  - Art Reference, circa 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Casting of Civitas, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork from Box 15, Folder 7, circa 1970-circa 1995 (Box 16)